<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Welcome to Zhiheng&#39;s Homepage</title>
    <link>http://cmccvic.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Welcome to Zhiheng&#39;s Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Zhiheng Liu</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cmccvic.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>IDC Network Design</title>
      <link>http://cmccvic.github.io/project/te/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cmccvic.github.io/project/te/</guid>
      <description> Provide Cloud design Private cloud traffic flow analysis Private cloud network design for china mobile private cloud </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MPLS-VPN MTU research in China Mobile IP private network</title>
      <link>http://cmccvic.github.io/project/mtu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cmccvic.github.io/project/mtu/</guid>
      <description> MPLS-VPN MTU research in China Mobile IP private network </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OPEN-O in Novonet</title>
      <link>http://cmccvic.github.io/project/novonet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cmccvic.github.io/project/novonet/</guid>
      <description>Job Role in NoveNet As the OPEN-O project manager to establish OPEN-O in NoveNet for field trail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SDN Multi-tenancy and Serveice Chain</title>
      <link>http://cmccvic.github.io/project/sdndc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cmccvic.github.io/project/sdndc/</guid>
      <description>Project Background Motivation(Before)  Users select the network, computing, storage of resources through the different page. To complete and bad user experience. Current CMCC DC pool can only allocate for less than 4K enterprise users. Besides, users can not customize their network. Network Function Virtualization(NFV) capacity is limited, can not provide users with value-added network services.  Objective(After)  Users can define their network resources, configuration, management, maintenance of private network through the graphical web interface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Engineering(TE) APP in SDN Controller</title>
      <link>http://cmccvic.github.io/project/sdnte/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cmccvic.github.io/project/sdnte/</guid>
      <description> Project Background Motivation  The average utilization of the backbone network is less than 50%. Network congestion reported.  Objective 骨干网内部整体轻载（全网均值利用率小于50%），但存在局部拥塞。骨干网缺少流量调度手段，可以在局部拥塞时调整流量去空闲路径 重要业务承载在CMNet网络上，需提供端到端的稳定带宽质量保障 VPN网络on demand业务的快速开通，可视化监控虚拟网络流量
Traffic Engineering(TE) APP Architecture Algorithm  Predictive algorithm Congestion algorithm Hybrid Traffic prediction algorithm Splitting algorithm  Field Trail Design of SDN TE in Fujian Metropolitan Area Network
Result  As IGW and IDC, third-party export, Railcom and other interconnection, simulated traffic scheduling IGW1-BR between the link utilization rate of 77%, IGW2-BR link between the utilization rate of 0% Using the Huawei traffic scheduling scheme to analyze the link flow information between IGW1 and BR, the elephant traffic between IGW1 and BR is adjusted to the link between IGW2 and BR After adjustment, the link bandwidth utilization between IGW1-BR and IGW2-BR is evenly distributed, averaging 40% and 37%  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zero Rating Service</title>
      <link>http://cmccvic.github.io/project/poster/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cmccvic.github.io/project/poster/</guid>
      <description> Poster for IEEE S&amp;amp;P 2017 Year: 2017 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OPEN-O</title>
      <link>http://cmccvic.github.io/project/openo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cmccvic.github.io/project/openo/</guid>
      <description>A Linux Foundation Project
Overview OPEN-O is seeking to offer network operators an incremental path to transform their networks, and OSS/BSS, through adoption of SDN and NFV without scrapping the vast investments in existing equipment and technologies.
OPEN-O Architecture The OPEN-O Architecture (shown in the Figure below), enables operators to orchestrate end-to- end composite services, leveraging virtualized (and physical network functions), and SDN and legacy connectivity services. The model-driven service framework uses standard modeling languages including TOSCA and YANG, and a modular approach to integrate with MANO building blocks (such as VIMs and VNFMs), along with Connectivity Services Management, including SDN Controllers, EMS’ and NMS’.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>